<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.smartesoft.smarteqm.mylyn.feature"
      label="SmarteQM Feature"
      version="2.3.1.qualifier"
      provider-name="SmarteSoft, Inc."
      plugin="com.smartesoft.smarteqm.mylyn.ui">

   <description url="http://www.smartesoft.com/SmarteQM/Downloads">
      This feature integrates SmarteQM with Eclipse using the Mylyn
task-focused interface. Useful for developers who want to be
able to review requirements, complete tasks and fix incidents
from within their existing Eclipse IDE user interface.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.smartesoft.com/SmarteQM">
      Copyright (C) 2006-2010 SmarteSoft Inc
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.smartesoft.com/SmarteQM">
 SMARTESOFT SOFTWARE EVALUATION AGREEMENT

The Products (defined below) are subject to the terms and conditions of this Software Evaluation Agreement
(“Agreement”). Accordingly, You (defined below) automatically accept the Products under the terms and conditions of this
Agreement (and are bound hereunder) when You click “Accept” (“Effective Date”), as You download a Product from
SmarteSoft, Inc. (“SmarteSoft”) or install a Product on a computer system. If You do not want to accept the Products
under the terms and conditions of this Agreement, then: (a) do not click “Accept”; (b) before installing a Product on a
computer system, destroy all originals and copies of the Products in Your possession, custody or control; and (c) certify in
writing to SmarteSoft that all such originals and copies have been so destroyed before such installation. Under this
Agreement, You and SmarteSoft are each a “party” and collectively the “parties.”

“You” means the person who downloads a software product from SmarteSoft or installs a software product from
SmarteSoft on a computer system. Any such software product is referenced herein as a “Product.” If You download or
install any revision or revised version of a Product, the definition of Products will automatically include such revision or
revised version.

1. LICENSE
SmarteSoft hereby grants You a nonexclusive, nontransferable, nonsublicensable, revocable license under SmarteSoft’s
intellectual property rights to: (a) install and use the Products, but only for the Purpose (defined below), on one (1) server
that has one (1) concurrent user; and (b) reproduce the Products, but only for the Purpose, as reasonably necessary for
such installation or use.

“Purpose” means Your personal testing, for only a non-commercial non-profit purpose, of: (a) software in which You own
the intellectual property rights; or (b) software for which You receive SmarteSoft’s prior written consent to such testing on
a software-by-software basis.

2. PAYMENTS

2.1 Taxes. You are responsible for, and will pay, all taxes, duties, levies and similar charges (including any related
interest and penalties), irrespective of how designated, in connection with the existence of (or activity under) this
Agreement. You will reimburse and indemnify SmarteSoft and hold SmarteSoft harmless for all such taxes, duties, levies
and charges that SmarteSoft is required to collect or remit to applicable authorities.

2.2 Costs &amp; Expenses. You will bear all of Your own costs and expenses in performing Your activity under this
Agreement (including, but not limited to, costs and expenses for supplies, facilities, utilities, management, employees,
travel, accommodation, and non-party intellectual property rights).

3. TERM &amp; TERMINATION

3.1 Term. The term of this Agreement will begin on the Effective Date and will continue in effect until it is terminated
under Section 3.2.

3.2 Breach. SmarteSoft may terminate this Agreement, effective immediately upon SmarteSoft informing You of
such termination.

3.3 Effect. Immediately upon termination of this Agreement: (a) all licenses to You under this Agreement are
automatically revoked; and (b) except as specified in Section 3.3(a), all other provisions of this Agreement will survive
beyond such termination in accordance with their terms and conditions.

3.4 Return of Products &amp; Material. Promptly after termination of this Agreement, You will: (a) either deliver to
SmarteSoft or destroy all originals and copies (irrespective of whether complete or partial) of Products in Your possession,
custody or control; (b) certify in writing to SmarteSoft that all such originals and copies have been so delivered or
destroyed; and (c) cease Your activity with Products.

4. INDEMNIFICATION

If a non-party’s claim against SmarteSoft arises from Your breach of this Agreement, You will indemnify SmarteSoft for all
amounts (e.g., damages and costs) owed by SmarteSoft to such non-party as a result of: (a) such claim; or (b) settlement
of such claim. Under this Section 4, You will also promptly reimburse SmarteSoft for its reasonable attorneys’ fees in
defending such claim and in conducting settlement negotiations.

5. REPRESENTATIONS, DISCLAIMERS, LIMITATIONS &amp; RESTRICTIONS

5.1 Disclaimer. EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY STATED TO THE CONTRARY ELSEWHERE IN THIS AGREEMENT,
SMARTESOFT AND ITS NON-PARTY LICENSORS HEREBY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND
WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTY OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NONINFRINGEMENT.

5.2 Limitation of Liability. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL
SMARTESOFT OR ITS NON-PARTY LICENSORS BE LIABLE UNDER THIS AGREEMENT FOR ANY DIRECT,
SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, EVEN
IF IT WAS AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, AND NOTWITHSTANDING FAILURE OF ESSENTIAL
PURPOSE OF ANY REMEDY.

5.3 Aggregate Liability. IN NO EVENT WILL THE AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF SMARTESOFT (AND ITS NONPARTY
LICENSORS) UNDER THIS AGREEMENT EXCEED ONE DOLLAR ($1.00), IRRESPECTIVE OF THE THEORY
OF LIABILITY, AND IRRESPECTIVE OF THE TYPE OF ACTION OR NUMBER OF CLAIMS.

5.4 High Risk Activity. You acknowledge, agree and understand that the Products are not fault-tolerant and that
You will not (and will neither cause nor permit any non-party to) use any Product for hazardous environments requiring
fail-safe performance, such as in the design, construction, operation or maintenance of any nuclear facility, aircraft control
or aircraft navigation systems, air traffic control, mass transit, direct life support machines, or weapons systems, in which
the failure of a Product could lead directly to death, personal injury, or severe physical or environmental damage (“High
Risk Activity”). Accordingly, SMARTESOFT AND ITS NON-PARTY LICENSORS SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIM ANY
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR HIGH RISK ACTIVITY.

5.5 Restriction. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in Section 1 or elsewhere in this Agreement, You
represent, warrant and covenant that, even while exercising Your license under Section 1: (a) except as expressly
permitted elsewhere in this Agreement, You will not (and will neither cause nor contractually permit any non-party to) use
or reproduce any Product; (b) except as expressly permitted by applicable law that cannot be waived, You will not (and
will neither cause nor contractually permit any non-party to) disassemble, decompile, decrypt, extract, or reverse engineer
any Product, nor otherwise apply any procedure or process to any Product in a manner that ascertains, derives, reveals
and/or appropriates the source code or source listings for any Product or for any algorithm, procedure, process or other
information contained in any Product; and (c) You will not (and will neither cause nor contractually permit any non-party
to) modify (e.g., prepare a derivative work based upon), sell, publish, or time share any Product, nor distribute (e.g.,
import, export) nor sublicense any Product, nor use or examine any Product for the purpose of patent assertion.
SmarteSoft will have no obligation to provide any service under this Agreement.

5.6 Consideration. YOU RECOGNIZE AND HEREBY AGREE THAT THE WARRANTY DISCLAIMERS AND
LIABILITY AND REMEDY LIMITATIONS IN THIS AGREEMENT ARE MATERIAL BARGAINED-FOR BASES OF THIS
AGREEMENT AND HAVE BEEN TAKEN INTO ACCOUNT AND REFLECTED IN DETERMINING THE
CONSIDERATION TO BE GIVEN BY EACH PARTY UNDER THIS AGREEMENT AND IN THE DECISION BY EACH
PARTY TO ENTER INTO THIS AGREEMENT.

6. MISCELLANEOUS

6.1 Assignment. You must not assign or transfer any right or obligation under this Agreement without SmarteSoft’s
written consent. A change in control is deemed an assignment subject to this Section. Any assignment, transfer, or
attempted assignment or transfer, in violation of this Section, is null and void. SmarteSoft may assign or transfer this
Agreement to any non-party, with or without Your consent. This Agreement inures to the benefit of SmarteSoft’s direct
and indirect successors, assignees and transferees.

6.2 Waiver. No breach of a provision of this Agreement will be deemed waived or excused, unless such waiver or
excuse is in writing and signed by SmarteSoft. Under this Agreement, SmarteSoft’s consents and approvals may be
withheld, delayed, conditioned or withdrawn at any time, for any or no reason, in SmarteSoft’s sole discretion.

6.3 Legal Fees. All remedies are cumulative and may be exercised concurrently or separately. If any action is
brought to enforce any provision of this Agreement or to declare a breach thereof, the prevailing party is entitled to
recover, in addition to any other amounts awarded, actual reasonable legal and other related costs and expenses,
including attorneys’ fees, incurred thereby.

6.4 Governing Law. This Agreement is governed by and construed and interpreted under the laws of the State of
Texas, USA, without reference to any rule of choice (or conflict) of laws. The United Nations Convention on Contracts for
the International Sale of Goods will not apply to this Agreement.

6.5 Dispute Resolution. Without diminishing either party’s rights under Section 6.6, any action involving any
dispute, controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement or the subject matter thereof, including any
question regarding its existence, validity, breach or termination, will be finally settled by binding arbitration in Austin,
Texas, USA, under the then-current commercial arbitration rules of the American Arbitration Association (“Rules“) by three
arbitrators in accordance with such Rules, as the sole dispute resolution mechanism. You and SmarteSoft will
respectively nominate one arbitrator for confirmation by the competent authority under the applicable Rules (“Appointing
Authority”). Both of such nominated arbitrators will agree on the third arbitrator within thirty (30) days; provided, however,
that if such nominated arbitrators fail to reach such agreement within such thirty (30) days, then the Appointing Authority
will appoint such third arbitrator. The procedural law of Texas will apply where the Rules are silent. The language to be
used in the arbitration proceeding will be English. Judgment upon any award made in such arbitration may be entered
and enforced in any court of competent jurisdiction.

6.6 Equitable Relief. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Agreement, in the event of a breach or
threatened breach by You of any provision of this Agreement, You hereby acknowledge and agree that SmarteSoft has
the right to seek immediate temporary or permanent injunctive relief, specific performance or other equitable relief, without
prejudice to any other rights and remedies available to SmarteSoft under this Agreement.

6.7 Headings. Titles and headings of paragraphs and sections within this Agreement are provided merely for
convenience and will not be used or relied upon in construing this Agreement or the parties’ intentions with respect
thereto.

6.8 Enforceability. If any portion of this Agreement is determined to be or becomes unenforceable or illegal, then
such portion will be reformed or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary for this Agreement to be enforceable and
legal, and this Agreement will remain in effect in accordance with its provisions as modified by such reformation or
elimination.

6.9 Ownership. As between You and SmarteSoft, You acknowledge and agree that SmarteSoft is the sole owner
throughout the world of all right, title and interest in and to the Products (including any copies thereof), together with all
patents, copyrights, trade secrets and other intellectual property rights available therein, resulting therefrom, or granted
pursuant thereto.

6.10 Compliance. In performing Your activity under this Agreement, You will comply at all times with all then-current
laws (including, but not limited to, foreign export laws and the United States export laws).

6.11 Audit. You will maintain accurate and complete books and records of Your activity under this Agreement for a
period of at least three (3) years after such activity, reasonably sufficient for SmarteSoft to verify Your compliance with this
Agreement. SmarteSoft may audit such books and records and Your activity with the Products (e.g., Your installations
and use of the Products) to verify Your compliance with this Agreement. You will reasonably cooperate in good faith with
such audit. If any such audit reveals that You have materially breached this Agreement, You will reimburse SmarteSoft
for its expenses incurred in conducting such audit. In conducting such audit, SmarteSoft may be assisted by its non-party
consultants.

6.12 Ordering Document. The terms and conditions of any ordering document (e.g., purchase order, order
acknowledgement form) that originates from You in connection with this Agreement will not be binding on SmarteSoft.

6.13 Restricted Rights. If a Product is being acquired by or on behalf of the U.S. Government or by a U.S.
Government prime contractor or subcontractor (at any tier), then the Government’s rights in the Product are only
“Restricted Rights” set forth in this Agreement, in accordance with 48 CFR 227.7201 through 227.7202-4 (for Department
of Defense (“DOD”) acquisitions) and with 48 CFR 2.101 and 12.212 (for non-DOD acquisitions). Under this Section, the
contractor and manufacturer is SmarteSoft, Inc., 400 West 15th Street, Suite 225, Austin, TX 78701.

6.14 Non-party Modules. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Agreement, if a software module of a
Product is governed under a non-party copyright license that conflicts with this Agreement (“Non-party Module”), then
such license (“Governing License”): (a) is identified, to SmarteSoft’s knowledge, within such Non-party Module or its
documentation; (b) is neither limited, expanded, preempted, nor otherwise modified by this Agreement; and (c) will prevail
over any conflicting provision of this Agreement (e.g., in governing Your permitted activity with such Non-party Module,
and in governing any non-party’s obligation or liability concerning such Non-party Module). The parties hereby
acknowledge and agree that no fee under this Agreement is attributable to any Non-party Module, notwithstanding
anything to the contrary elsewhere in this Agreement.

6.15 Order of Precedence. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Agreement, if the parties have entered
into a prior written agreement that was mutually signed by their respectively authorized representatives, and if this
Agreement conflicts with such prior written agreement, then such prior written agreement will prevail to the extent of such
conflict.

6.16 Entire Agreement. This Agreement constitutes the sole and exclusive terms and conditions between the
parties relating to the subject matter hereof, and supersedes all prior discussions, writings, negotiations, understandings
and agreements with respect thereto, and will not be amended except by a written amendment that is accepted and
agreed by each party. By accepting the Products under the terms and conditions of this Agreement, You acknowledge
that You have read, understand and agree to this Agreement as being effective for all purposes as of the Effective Date,
notwithstanding any other date set forth elsewhere.

   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="SmarteSoft Download Site" url="http://www.smartesoft.com/Downloads/Eclipse"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import feature="org.eclipse.mylyn_feature" version="3.3.2.v20100222-0100-e3x"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.smartesoft.smarteqm.mylyn.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.smartesoft.smarteqm.mylyn.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
